<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Crisis management</string>
    <string name="autor">Author: José Luis Peñuela Berenguer</string>
    <string name="btnCrear">Create</string>
    <string name="btnDimitir">Retire</string>
    <string name="btnGestionar">Manage</string>
    <string name="btnJugar">Play</string>
    <string name="btnOrtodoxa">orthodox</string>
    <string name="btnPuntuaciones">Scores</string>
    <string name="crisis">Crisis managed</string>
    <string name="datosJugadorTitulo">Player data</string>
    <string name="dificultad">Difficulty</string>
    <string name="dificultadDificil">Hard</string>
    <string name="dificultadExplicacion">Select difficulty level</string>
    <string name="dificultadFacil">Easy</string>
    <string name="dificultadNormal">Normal</string>
    <string name="exito">Succesful management</string>
    <string name="fondoPantalla">Alternative background</string>
    <string name="usuarioVacio">Enter user name</string>
    <string name="txtTituloCrisis">CURRENT CRISIS</string>
    <string name="txtShock">Apply shock policy</string>
    <string name="txtProblema">The crisis your are facing is...</string>
    <string name="txtPolitica">Aply policy</string>
    <string name="txtEstado">STATE OF THE NATION</string>
    <string name="txtEconomia">Economy level: %1$d</string>
    <string name="txtAyudaInternacional">Ask for international help</string>
    <string name="txtDerechos">Social rigths level: %1$d</string>
    <string name="txtAprobacion">Agreement level: %1$d</string>
    <string name="tituloPrincipal">Crisis management</string>
    <string name="radioMujer">Female</string>
    <string name="radioHombre">Male</string>
    <string name="marcador">Score</string>
    <string name="listaPuntuaciones">Scores</string>
    <string name="introducirNombre">Enter user name</string>
    <string name="fondoPantallaExplicacion">Change main window background color</string>
    <string name="genero">Select the gender of your player</string>
    <string name="instruccionesLayout">Instructions</string>
    <string name="opciones">Options</string>
    <string name="btnInstrucciones">Instructions</string>
    <string name="autorAction">Author</string>
    <string name="resultadoPolitica">Result of the last policy applied</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Information</string>
    <string name="disclaimerAction">To use this application it is neede and API higher than 21</string>
    <string name="btnAceptarInternacional">Accept</string>
    <string name="btnCancelarInternacional">Reject</string>
    <string name="txtAyudaInternacionalActivity">Here you can ask the international community for help, they may decide to help you, do nothing or punish you, so meditate calmly if the economy is bad enough to require help. \\n\\nWhether you select international aid or not, you will no longer be allowed to ask for it until the next crisis.</string>
    <string name="txtTituloInternacional">International help</string>
    <string name="btnAyudaInternacional">Help</string>
    <string name="endGame">Your result has been %1$s points</string>
    <string name="instruccionesDetalle">The game is to manage as many crises as possible. The game ends when you press the button retire or when you fail in three consecutive crises.   In the case retiring the points would be saved, in the case of failing in the three crises the score is 0.   If you use the orthodox policy button then you give a small boost to the crisis, but the use of panic policy can either bring a big success, a big failure or leave things as they are.   There is a last option where you can ask an international body for help. They can leave things as they are, make them better or worse.</string>
    <string name="radioVacio">Please select a gender</string>
    <string name="txtGestion">FREEDONIA</string>
    <string name="txtFallosConsecutivos">Number of Strikes:</string>
    <string name="introduccion">The people of freedonia have chosen you to manage the country\'s march. Courageously face the crises that the country will have to endure and gain a place in the history of the great nation of freedonia.</string>
    <string name="btnPanico">Panic !!!</string>
    <string name="crisis1">The workers are demanding better wages and working conditions. To achieve this, they have called a strike that has paralysed the whole country; the destruction in the streets and in the shops is considerable. It is time for you to manage this crisis and implement a policy.</string>
    <string name="crisis2">Pensioners do not agree with their pensions and are asking for an increase of at least 20%. To put pressure on our government team they have started going to the doctor with false ailments to get free prescriptions. If we continue at this rate, spending on medicines will put a hole in our budgets. You need to implement a policy as quickly as possible.</string>
    <string name="crisis3">At the moment we are suffering from a massive exodus of young people who are leaving the country in search of a dignified life. If this continues, in the end there will be no one left to pay taxes and the entire government structure will fall by its own weight. Apply a policy as quickly as possible to stop this exodus.</string>
    <string name="noDisponible">This option is not available at this moment</string>
</resources>